var config = [

	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "What is the empirical formula of a hydrocarbon with 75 % carbon and 25 % hydrogen by mass?",
		answers: ["C₃H", "CH₂", "C₂H₆", "CH₄"],
		correct: 4
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "What is the ground state electron configuration of an atom of chromium, Cr (Z = 24)?",
		answers: ["[Ar]3d⁶", "[Ar]4s²3d⁴", "[Ar]4s¹3d⁵", "[Ar]4s²4p⁴"],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "What are the principal energy level number and number of valence electrons for an atom of bismuth, Bi (Z = 83)?",
		answers: ["5, 3", "5, 5", "6, 5", "6, 15"],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which series represents atoms in order of decreasing atomic radius?",
		answers: ["N > C > Be > Mg", "Mg > N > C > Be", "Be > C > N > Mg", "Mg > Be > C > N"],
		correct: 4
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which electrons are removed from iron (Z = 26) to form iron(II)?",
		answers: ["two 3d electrons", "two 4s electrons", "one 4s electron and one 3d electron", "two 4p electrons"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "What is the order of increasing boiling point?",
		answers: ["CH₃CH₂CH₂CH₃ < CH₃CH(OH)CH₃ < CH₃COCH₃ < CH₃CO₂H", "CH₃CH₂CH₂CH₃ < CH₃COCH₃ < CH₃CH(OH)CH₃ < CH₃CO₂H", "CH₃CO₂H < CH₃COCH₃ < CH₃CH(OH)CH₃ < CH₃CH₂CH₂CH₃", "CH₃CH₂CH₂CH₃ < CH₃COCH₃ < CH₃CO₂H < CH₃CH(OH)CH₃"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "What is the IUPAC name of NiCO₃?",
		answers: ["nickel(II) carbonate", "nickel carbonate", "nickel(I) carbonate", "nitrogen(I) carbonate"],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Strong metallic bonds have a ____ charge on the metal ion and a ____ radius.",
		answers: ["large, large", "large, small", "small, large", "small, small"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which species has delocalized electrons?",
		answers: ["OH⁻", "H₂CO", "CO₂", "CO₃²⁻"],
		correct: 4
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "When equal masses of X and Y absorb the same amount of energy, their temperatures rise by 5 °C and 10 °C respectively. Which is correct?",
		answers: ["The specific heat capacity of X is twice that of Y.", "The specific heat capacity of X is half that of Y.", "The specific heat capacity of X is one fifth that of Y.", "The specific heat capacity of X is the same as Y."],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which is correct for the reaction H₂O(g) → H₂O(l)?",
		answers: ["Enthalpy increases and entropy increases.", "Enthalpy decreases and entropy increases.", "Enthalpy increases and entropy decreases.", "Enthalpy decreases and entropy decreases."],
		correct: 4
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which equation represents the standard enthalpy of atomization of bromine, Br₂?",
		answers: ["½Br₂(l) → Br(g)", "Br₂(l) → 2Br(g)", "Br₂(l) → 2Br(l)", "½Br₂(l) → Br(l)"],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which is correct for a reaction with a positive change in Gibbs free energy, ΔGᶿ?",
		answers: ["The formation of reactants is favoured.", "The formation of products is favoured.", "The reaction is at equilibrium.", "The reaction is spontaneous."],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which solution is basic at 25 °C? (Kw = 1.0 × 10⁻¹⁴)",
		answers: ["[H⁺] = 1.0 × 10⁻³ moldm⁻³", "[OH⁻] = 1.0 × 10⁻¹³ moldm⁻³", "solution of pH = 4.00", "[H₃O⁺] = 1.0 × 10⁻¹³ moldm⁻³"],
		correct: 4
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which is a Lewis acid but not a Brønsted−Lowry acid?",
		answers: ["AlCl₃", "CH₃CO₂H", "HF", "CCl₄"],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which has the strongest conjugate base?",
		answers: ["HCOOH (Kₐ = 1.8 × 10⁻⁴)", "HNO₂ (Kₐ = 7.2 × 10⁻⁴)", "HCN (Kₐ = 6.2 × 10⁻¹⁰)", "HIO₃ (Kₐ = 1.7 × 10⁻¹)"],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which product will be obtained at the anode (positive electrode) when molten NaCl is electrolysed?",
		answers: ["Na(l)", "Cl(g)", "Cl₂(g)", "Na(s)"],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Where does oxidation occur in a voltaic cell?",
		answers: ["positive electrode and anode", "negative electrode and anode", "positive electrode and cathode", "negative electrode and cathode"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which is not a requirement of the standard hydrogen electrode (SHE)?",
		answers: ["V = 1 dm³", "p(H₂) = 100 kPa", "use of platinum as the electrode material", "[H₃O⁺] = 1 moldm⁻³"],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which is a major product of the electrophilic addition of hydrogen chloride to propene?",
		answers: ["ClCH₂CH=CH₂", "CH₃CH(Cl)CH₃", "CH₃CH₂CH₂Cl", "CH₃CH=CHCl"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which alcohol would produce a carboxylic acid when heated with acidified potassium dichromate(VI)?",
		answers: ["propan-2-ol", "butan-1-ol", "2-methylpropan-2-ol", "pentan-3-ol"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which solvent is aprotic?",
		answers: ["H₂O", "C₆H₅CH₃", "CH₃OH", "CH₃NH₂"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which statement is not correct regarding benzene?",
		answers: ["It is planar.", "The ring contains delocalized electrons.", "It always reacts in the same way as alkenes.", "The carbon–carbon bond has a bond order of 1.5."],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "How should a measurement of 5.00 g from a balance be recorded?",
		answers: ["5.00 ± 0.1 g", "5.00 ± 0.01 g", "5.00 ± 1 g", "5.00 ± 0.001 g"],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		level: "1",
		theme: "chem",
		question: "Which can be identified using infrared (IR) spectroscopy?",
		answers: ["functional groups", "molar mass", "3-D configuration", "bond angle"],
		correct: 1
	},

];
